and
We'll be right back.
But you were really looking forward to watching Kaze Haya play today, weren't you?
You see, hearing he played baseball in middle school, I made it my goal to witness it. It became important to me.
All I wanted was to see a side of Kaze Haya I didn't know yet.
Is that so? Are you saying that you actually know things about him then?
Cause I don't think you do.
Don't treat my feelings the same way as yours.
I've always watched Kaze Haya. It's something I've done ever since we were in middle school together.
On rainy days.
Really?
On windy days.
No way!
Even on snowy days.
In the cold too?
So, then, whenever I would see him talking to other girls, I'd intervene and try to prevent him from dating any of them.
You...
You've worked so hard!
Oh, well, yeah! Of course I have!
Man, that was a close one.
But anyway, the point is, I can confidently say I know Kaze Haya quite well.
And it's not as if this is anything new either.
Like I was saying, I've watched over him forever.
You're out!
Let's keep this up!
Yeah!
It's impossible...
to keep your eyes off him.
Don't try to act like you understand how I feel.
Suddenly, Kaze Haya is right there in front of me.
And I can't look away.
Before I know it, I'm already thinking about him.
As I'm falling asleep, his face immediately comes to mind.
Everything is a first for me.
I thought this feeling I was experiencing was something special.
I'm very aware of the fact that I don't know that much about myself.
Or about Kaze Haya, either.
Would I still feel the same way I've been feeling lately
if it was someone other than him?
Perhaps there's something more beyond this I haven't been able to grasp yet.
I want to know.
To be honest, I want to learn more about him.
About my own feelings.
I have to know more.
Strike! And you're out!
I'll try talking to Sanada to understand him better.
I'm really grateful for all of your help.
Did she accept my challenge?
No matter what, I'm going to keep doing things my way until I get what I want.
Uh, but wait, the game isn't over yet.
Huh?
D-did she not want to sit here and watch it with me?
Ugh.
When it comes to Kurumi,
I can't even imagine how special Kaze Haya must be to her.
She's known him for so long.
I want him to be my boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Oh, I see.
So are feelings for him are romantic.
Romantic feelings?
Romantic feelings.
I think this is the first time I've clearly recognized and processed those words.
Thanks a lot for the good game.
Yeah!
We actually won!
I'm so glad.
Congrats on the win, Kaze Haya.
Congrats, everyone.
Oh, that's right.
Kurumi never did come back.
Oh, jeez.
You were here the whole time?
When your hairstyle's different,
it's pretty hard to know it's you.
Hi, Endo.
Call me Tomo.
Isn't it great?
We won!
Yeah.
We're going to cheer for the volleyball game next.
You should come with us.
What?
Can I?
You sure?
What are you talking about?
Weren't you planning to show your support for Ayana and Jizu?
Echo's playing too.
Come on.
Let's get going.
Oh, no.
I didn't say anything wrong.
Did I, Soliko?
No.
It's just...
I'm happy.
Thank you.
I'd love to.
Mm-hmm.
Being alone was normal for me until recently.
But now...
I have so many kind-hearted people in my life.
I'm sure if even one of them was missing,
things would have turned out much differently.
And of course, if Kazehaya wasn't around, then I never would have known that anyone could be this kind.
I'm so grateful for him.
My world has changed drastically.
Admiration, respect, romantic feelings.
I don't know my own feelings.
But I want to learn.
I want to find out more about them.
It makes him the same as Kazehaya, doesn't it?
If I talk to Sanada, will I learn more?
Will I be able to find an answer?
Come on, let's get back.
Yeah, what's next?
I think it might be girls volleyball and boys soccer?
Hmm?
Hey, uh, so earlier.
Earlier?
Uh, uh, are you into Kuro Numa?
Ah, Sakako.
Or wait, no, Sawako?
Right?
Her name's Kuro Numa.
Kuro Numa?
Kuro!
Oh, so you mean like black.
I will admit that I actually like Kuriyama.
But none of the way you're probably thinking, Shota.
It's Kuro Numa.
Huh?
Is that not what I said?
You said Yama again.
Did I?
What?
This about that curveball?
No, just forget it.
I caught it because I was the closest.
Yeah, I know that.
I know, but...
My first thought after it happened was,
I wish I had caught it instead.
Hmm.
Looks like girls soccer and boys softball won their first matches.
That means free barbecue.
Mr. Peen.
Huh?
I'd like to check the field day committee members' schedule
if you wouldn't mind showing me.
Mm-hmm.
I need their year in class.
And their name.
Oh, um...
Actually, I'm pretty sure I can look that much up on my own.
What the...
No way!
Just tell me and I can give you the info.
I mean...
I would, but...
I really don't want to inconvenience you.
What is with this kid?
Here.
I really appreciate it.
Kazehaya is...
There.
He's cleaning up equipment in the afternoon
and then carrying it to the storage room.
Once you're done with your business, get out of here.
Okay.
Thank you so much, Mr. Peen.
If you'll please excuse me.
Uh, sure.
What's with that over-excessive smiling?
It's creepy.
Without fail,
I have always watched over Kazehaya.
Now, which one should I get for Chizu?
Oh.
If it isn't Miss Kurumi.
Uh, you're Aya and Ayano, isn't that right?
And I believe you're friends with Sawako and Chizu.
Uh-huh.
I heard that you went to Chizu's middle school.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, uh, I'm curious.
What skin toner do you use?
I don't... use any.
Huh?
I'm using a face mask tonight.
My sister's expensive one.
I'm honestly surprised you knew my name.
Oh, right.
I guess there were all those rumors.
Rumors?
Don't worry about things like that.
People who spread gossip are just troubled.
That's true.
And the ones who believe them are stupid.
By the way, I'm assuming you heard the rumors, too.
Did you talk to anyone about them?
No way!
I never trusted any of that nonsense.
I just overheard it from a group of girls who were discussing it one day.
Oh, of course.
Can't imagine someone like you ever spreading gossip.
That's nice of you to say.
You know, I have this theory.
The rumors were spread by someone who likes Kaze Haya.
I bet Sawako was in the way so the person felt threatened.
And if me and Chizu were Sawako's backup, it'd be difficult to mess with her.
Plus, putting aside what was said about me,
a majority of Chizu's rumors were slightly exaggerated things that actually happened.
And knowing that is why I think it was someone who went to the same middle school as Chizu and Kaze Haya.
But I wonder what that girl's gonna do if Kaze Haya finds out about this.
Who's to say?
Though, you can't accuse someone if there isn't any evidence.
So you can't.
Looks like we ended up talking for a while, huh?
We did.
The game's starting up soon, so I think I'll get going.
Well, I wish you luck with everything.
Yeah.
You too, Ayane.
Thanks, Sia.
Oh, by the way,
she's surprisingly tough, isn't she?
Since she plays fair and square.
Wait, Kaze Haya has another game?
Yeah, you don't remember?
He's also got field day committee work.
Ryu, what are you gonna do after this?
Eating a nap, probably.
Really?
Lunch already?
And then a little siesta, huh?
Trash?
But my nap.
Uh, what's wrong?
You okay?
Oh, man.
Guess I can nap outside.
What?
Where at?
Maybe somewhere near the PE equipment room?
Uh, why in a place like that?
Who cares?
Let him sleep where he wants.
Tough?
Yeah, right.
My calculations were a bit off, that's all.
Good job, guys.
Thought you could use these.
Thanks, you read my mind, Sadako.
All right, now tell me, how did I do out there?
Oh, my gosh, you were amazing.
And very red.
Stop it.
You're making me blush.
Guess you got your money's worth out of that shirt.
What should we do?
Go get lunch?
Works for me.
Are you feeling hungry, too?
Yeah!
Um, I have some business that I should probably take care of.
What kind?
A softball almost hit me during the game earlier, but Sanada saved me by catching it, so I wanted
to say thanks to him.
Yeah?
Ryu did that?
Wow, he did something good for once.
Also, there's something that I was planning to look into.
Huh?
At the moment, I'm a bit lost and confused, and I don't even know how I can begin to explain,
but, um, once I manage to figure everything out for myself, will you two be here to listen?
Hmm?
I'm not sure I get what you're talking about, but...
We'd be more than happy to.
Thank you so much.
I'll see you later, then.
By the way, Sawako, don't be fooled, okay?
You need to make sure that you always prioritize your own feelings, no matter what.
Huh?
What was that about?
Let's just say, Sawako has a lot to think about and try to sort out on her own.
Wait, she does?
Which means we have a bit of business to take care of ourselves.
Whoa, Yano-Chin has an evil look on her face.
Hey, Sawako!
Oh, hi!
Did you find Sanada?
I saw him earlier, if you need...
Why are you looking at me like that?
You...
You just called out to me!
I was worried because you left before the game was over, and I thought I said something to offend you!
Huh?
Jeez!
You are so annoying!
Wasn't that amazing?
I had totally...
Anyway, I saw Sanada go towards the PE equipment room earlier.
Thanks for letting me know, Kurumi.
Well, she's not that tough, just really difficult.
Uh, um, Sanada?
Hmm?
Oh, hey, you're here.
Uh, I am?
Kuro...
Uh...
I just read it from this.
Hold on.
Whoa.
It says exactly what I've been thinking about on this piece of paper.
But how?
Um...
Remember when you saved my life earlier?
I wanted to say thank you for that.
It's because of you that I can continue to live my life.
Nah, I really don't think that curveball had enough power in it to kill anybody.
I'm very grateful to you.
Oh...
For me?
Is that all?
Um...
Actually, I was hoping that I could talk to you for a little bit.
What about?
Well...
Would you mind explaining to me what romantic feelings are like?
Romantic feelings?
Basically, it's when you like someone, but not quite liking them as a friend.
It's something a bit more special.
No, I know what it is.
Hmm...
I'll tell you.
My eyes are only for Chizuru.
It's a secret.
I...
I think you two are made for each other.
Quite the compliment.
Kasehaya!
Oh, hey.
You look pretty busy.
Would you like some help?
This is...
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
I was just thinking.
If you asked Kuro Numa if she needed help, she'd probably say,
This is my mission.
Hey, Kasehaya, is it true you rejected Sawako before summer break?
Huh?
Whoa, are people seriously still spreading that around?
I didn't do that.
Is that so?
I mean, honestly, it's not like Kuro Numa even asked me out in the first place.
After all, for her to want to do that, she'd have to actually like me.
That makes sense.
When I asked if she wanted to go out with you, she said not a chance.
Also, I happened to notice that she wasn't paying attention to you at all earlier.
Wait, when earlier?
During the softball game, I noticed that she kept looking over at Sanada.
A person saves you from something like that, and it's not surprising that you'd fall for them.
If she likes him, then we should give them our support.
I bet she'd appreciate that.
So, Sanada, can you tell me how long you've liked Yoshida?
How long has it been?
What sparked those feelings?
What was it?
And how did you know that she was someone special to you?
Well, uh...
Do I have to give you a logical answer for that?
By the time I noticed, she was already special to me.
No one else can compare to her.
If someone's incomparable, would they be special?
I don't know.
Is that what you want?
If true?
If...
It was true?
You see?
I told you.
Well, let's give them all our support, okay?
Hey.
Thank you.
That's what I felt. Very, very, very strongly. Next time, love.